tozlugiyim.com.tr 2017-12-26

# Kullanım Koşulları - Tozlu.Com/EN

This agreement contains the privacy policy of tozlu.com (TOZLU TEKSTİL SANAYİ VE TİCARET AŞ). By visiting tozlu.com website you agree to obey the rules listed below. 

Tozlu.com requires some of your personal information at the membership phase. Protecting your personal information and maintaining your privacy is a crucial priority of the tozlu.com team. Therefore the information you have given will not be used except for the purposes of the rules in the membership agreement and will not be shared with third parties. In order to determine the system-related problems and to solve them as quickly as possible, when necessary tozlu.com identifies users’ IP address and uses it. IP addresses can also be used to define the users in a general way and to gather broad demographic information. 

Registration forms, order forms, surveys and competitions, your contact information (your name, surname, email address, telephone numbers, and mailing address) are demanded on our website. Your personal information written above is used to get your orders, to provide our products and services, to perform your payment, to deliver your orders, to give information about your order, to contact with you for marketing purposes.

When user becomes a member of tozlu.com, unless you request, daily and weekly informational and marketing e-mails will be sent to your email address. 

You have the right to make changes, or not to receive these e-mails. The content of these emails can contain the purchased product or product-related information, other products that we think you may be interested, 3.Persons’ advertisements and similar information. Demographic information will be used to determine our members shopping interest as a marketing strategy of Tozlu.com. 

Only employees who need to access your personal information to perform a specific job (editing of special promotional activities and not to forward unsolicited e-mail, customer classification, etc.) are granted access to your personal information.

Tozlu.com does not share any personal information collected during the shopping, without the customer's authorization, and does not use them outside of Tozlu.com. Tozlu.com has the right to share customers` information only in needs of official demands stated by the government and/or laws. In all other cases Tozlu.com does not share customer’s information with any third party. All payment and customer information is protected by the industry standard data protection SSL Secure 128 m/byte. No credit card information is stored on Tozlu.com servers. Our servers only act as a bridge between the customer and bank computers.

You can send us an email for all your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy from the contact section in our website. You can do it by sending email your membership cancellation of tozlu.com to support@tozlu.com address or making transactions “unsubscribe” option located in the “my account” tab in the tozlu.com. You can find our contact information below to the tozlu.com. Customers can request a free written information about themselves to learn what information is saved. Your requests about possible fixes, blocking or deletion of information are taken process immediately to the extent provided by law. We may request your personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number to respond to your requests and wishes, in order to fulfill these requests or manage interactive customer programs. Sharing this information with us and being a member to the address of tozlu.com will be made with your request and your confirmation. At any time if you want to get out from our daily email send list, you can get out with single click by clicking the link of at the bottom of the e-mail that we have sent “Please click here to get out from our email list”. 

Address: TOZLU TEKSTİL SANAYİ VE TİCARET AŞ Atatürk Bulv. No: 286 Tekkeköy/ Samsun/TURKEY

Phone: +90 362 266 98 49 Customer Service: +90 850 766 55 55

Email: support@tozlu.com
